# VICTOR PEREIRA

Lawrenceville GA, 30043 | 404-790-2879 | victor5055@outlook.com

## PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Skilled professional with 10 years of diverse and progressive experience in positions with increasing responsibility in sales and customer service. Accomplished, decisive, flexible and works well under pressure when faced with unexpected situations, thriving in a fast-paced environment. Builds strong relationships with customers and associates to elevate brand awareness. Recognized for efficiency improvements and increased productivity. Utilizes proven management experience to align business development objectives with organizational goals, strengthening customer relationships, team building, and revenue growth.

CORE COMPETENCIES		
<ul> <li>✓ Exceptional Customer Service</li> <li>✓ Business Development &amp; Marketing</li> <li>✓ Project Management</li> <li>✓ Trilingual (English, Portuguese, Spanish)</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>✓ Leadership &amp; Team Building</li> <li>✓ Strategic Brand Building</li> <li>✓ Inventory Management</li> <li>✓ Attention to Detail</li> </ul>	<ul><li>✓ Exceptional Communication</li><li>✓ Troubleshooting</li><li>✓ Budget Management</li><li>✓ Problem Solving</li></ul>
Professional Experience		

#### Marcos and Elezete House Cleaning Service | Atlanta, GA

January 2009 - Present

Manager

Trained new staff members in all aspects of house cleaning, ensuring that they meet health and safety standards.

- Reduced the amount spent on chemical cleaner by \$200 per home through effective cost management and adopting natural cleaners.
- Established and maintained clean and comfortable home environments by performing cleaning duties, including vacuuming, cleaning windows, dusting, and bathrooms.
- Reported any damage, maintenance problems, safety issues, and potential hazards to management, ensuring adherence to safety code procedures.
- Completed tasks per customer request, serving every customer as a VIP.

#### Fogo de Chão | Atlanta, GA

April 2014 – Present

Server/Gaucho Meat Server

Trained servers on new and existing culinary procedures and execution; prepared a variety of foods, such as meats, vegetables, desserts, according to customers' orders or supervisors' instructions, following approved procedures.

- Partnered with culinary innovations team to vet new menu and beverage items, ensuring they were operationally sound;
   collected customer feedback and made necessary adjustments.
- Presented menus to patrons and answered questions about menu items, making recommendations upon request.
- Trained new servers in providing excellent customer service and conflict resolution techniques.

### Chepe's Mexican Grill | Cumming, GA

June 2010 - May 2014

Server/Bartender/Team Leader

Led and coached staff in all aspects of culinary execution and influenced daily restaurant operations achieving positive results through building sales, developing the team in inventory, ordering, staffing, labor management, productivity, strategic planning, and guest satisfaction.

Memorized restaurant's menu and appropriate drink pairings, leading to a 15% increase in sales.

#### **EDUCATION**

Georgia Perimeter College, Dunwoody, GA